Cover Letter

Pradeep

Bikram

Thapa

Trinity International College

Tribhuvan University

22nd April, 2023

Mulpani

22nd April, 2023

Your Ref: 348

Ms Bandana

ShahHR

Manager

NewNepTech

Durbarmarg, Kathmandu,

NepalDear Miss Shah

I wish to apply for the post of Jr. Technician writer, which was advertised in this month's IT magazine.

I am currently a junior technician at Nepal Telecom where I have 3 years' experience of developing user-friendly technical documents. I am familiar with technical writing standards and guidelines.

Prior to taking over my current post, I worked in Tribhuvan Int'l Airport as a Senior Technician, where I was involved in working with System Architects, Analysts, Engineering, Testing, and Technical Support teams to obtain an in-depth understanding of the product and the documentation requirements.

My experience in the fields of both Senior and Junior Technical services has given me the necessary commercial and technical awareness to be able to make a valuable contribution to the technical writing of your client.

Please let me know if there is any further information you

require. I look forward to hearing from you.

Yours

sincerely

Pradeep Thapa

Enc:

Curriculum Vitae

Personal details Name: Pradeep Thapa

Age: 26

Date of Birth: 30 April, 1997

Marital Status: Single

Address: Mulpani,

Tel: 9860997587

Position applied for: Jr. Technical Writer

Education

2000 to 2012 Mount Glory School, Dallu, Kathmandu

General Certificate of Education

Mathematics B+

English A+

Nepali B+

Science A+

Computer A+

2012 to 2014 Trinity International College, Dillibazaar, Kathmandu

+2 including computer science

2014 to 2018 Tribhuvan University, Kirtipur

Bachelor of Computer Application (BCA)

Work experience

2020 to present Company: Nepal Telecom

Post: Jr. Technician

Responsibilities: developing user-friendly technical documents to

cover aspects such as configuration and online help.

2018 to 2020 Company: Tribhuvan International Airport (TIA)

Post: Senior Technician

Responsibilities: working with System Analysts, Engineering, Testing,

Technical Support teams to obtain an in-depth understanding of the

product and the documentation requirements.

Other information clean driving licence

Referees

Pratap Babu Tiwari Sunil Paudel

General Manager Managing Director

Tribhuvan Int'l Nepal Telecom

Airport

Koteshwor Tripureshwor

Kathmandu Kathmandu

Current Salary Rs. 60,000